<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greenwashings on Greenwashing</title>
    <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Greenwashings on Greenwashing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>  Billions Of Bird Killed For Fashion Says Designer Mccartney</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/billions-of-bird-killed-for-fashion-says-designer-mccartney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/billions-of-bird-killed-for-fashion-says-designer-mccartney/</guid>
      <description>British designer Stella McCartney expressed her concern over the  billions of birds  killed for the fashion industry during her Paris show, which she titled  It s about&amp;hellip; time.  The event, held near the Eiffel Tower, showcased sustainable fashion pieces made from unconventional materials like lentils and mushroom leather. McCartney, daughter of ex-Beatle Paul McCartney and animal rights activist Linda McCartney, is an advisor to luxury tycoon Bernard Arnault on sustainability.  Bird motifs were prominent in her spring-summer collection, where she combined her signature business suits and jackets with delicate blouses and dresses. McCartney aimed to balance the  masculinity  of some cuts with a  lightness of touch  and  femininity in flight.  She also highlighted her use of  apple leather  made from waste in the apple industry and metallic bras shaped like birds.  The designer, a lifelong vegetarian, has long advocated for sustainability in fashion, with her brand praised for its innovation and transparency. The fashion industry, however, faces criticism for its environmental impact, with some brands accused of greenwashing.  The show was attended by Hollywood figures such as Greta Gerwig, Natalie Portman, and Hayley Williams. The event also saw protests at Hermes Paris Fashion Week, where the luxury house is known for its leather goods. Despite this, McCartney s commitment to sustainable fashion remains a significant influence in the industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Unmasking Corporate Deception: Recent Examples of False Eco-Friendly Claims&#34;</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world, more people care about the environment. But some companies pretend to be eco-friendly to trick consumers, investors, and the public. This is called &amp;ldquo;greenwashing.&amp;rdquo; They hide bad practices behind a fake green image. Let&amp;rsquo;s look at some recent examples to understand this better.
A big company recently said it aims to have Net Zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2050, with smaller goals by 2030. This sounds good, but there&amp;rsquo;s more to the story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2024 Pennsylvania general election voter guide : Treasurer</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/2024-pennsylvania-general-election-voter-guide-treasurer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/2024-pennsylvania-general-election-voter-guide-treasurer/</guid>
      <description>The candidates for Pennsylvania Treasurer in the 2024 general election have outlined their visions for improving the State Treasurer s office and increasing transparency. Erin McClelland (Democrat) proposes expanding the database of state contracts to include vendor demographics and compliance with US trade policies. She also suggests reinstating pension investment standards and increasing transparency by acknowledging errors and incorporating ESG ratings.  Stacy Garrity (Republican) emphasizes building on her achievements, such as returning unclaimed property and earning a Gold Rating for the PA 529 College &amp;amp; Career Program. She plans to continue cutting fees for savings programs and improve transparency by adding new features to the Transparency Portal and revamping the Fiscal Health Scorecard.  Nickolas Ciesielski (Libertarian) focuses on reducing state debt and eliminating state pensions, proposing a shift to a 457 retirement plan and including Bitcoin in state investment funds. He advocates for a more detailed breakdown of investment pools and a crowdsourced auditing system.  Troy Bowman (Constitution County, Allegheny) and Chris Foster (Forward County, Allegheny) have not provided specific proposals. However, Bowman emphasizes serving all Pennsylvanians and enhancing transparency, while Foster highlights fiscal responsibility and collaboration for a secure financial future.  Overall, the candidates aim to increase transparency, accountability, and fiscal responsibility in the State Treasurer s office, with varying approaches to addressing state debt, investment policies, and public access to information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alaska Air Group Announces Proposed Senior Secured Notes Offering</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/alaska-air-group-announces-proposed-senior-secured-notes-offering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/alaska-air-group-announces-proposed-senior-secured-notes-offering/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America largest corn company hired an Iowa repeat offender</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/america-largest-corn-company-hired-an-iowa-repeat-offender/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/america-largest-corn-company-hired-an-iowa-repeat-offender/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Power Group Closes $1 . 3 Million Private Placement with Its Largest Shareholder</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/american-power-group-closes-1-3-million-private-placement-with-its-largest-shareholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/american-power-group-closes-1-3-million-private-placement-with-its-largest-shareholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Modernization Services Market worth $39 . 62 billion by 2029 - Exclusive Report by MarketsandMarkets™</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/application-modernization-services-market-worth-39-62-billion-by-2029-exclusive-report-by-marketsandmarketstm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/application-modernization-services-market-worth-39-62-billion-by-2029-exclusive-report-by-marketsandmarketstm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ascendant Resources Approved for EU Sponsored Cutting - Edge Geophysical  Undercover  Program at Its Lagoa Salgada Project</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/ascendant-resources-approved-for-eu-sponsored-cutting-edge-geophysical-undercover-program-at-its-lagoa-salgada-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/ascendant-resources-approved-for-eu-sponsored-cutting-edge-geophysical-undercover-program-at-its-lagoa-salgada-project/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AsianInvestor takes a short break for National Day | From the Editor</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/asianinvestor-takes-a-short-break-for-national-day-from-the-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/asianinvestor-takes-a-short-break-for-national-day-from-the-editor/</guid>
      <description>October 1 in Hong Kong is observed as a public holiday in commemoration of the National Day. On this day, the daily newsletter and the weekly ESG newsletter will not be published. The publication activities will resume on the following day, October 2. In light of this, the publishers extend their warm wishes to all readers for a joyous and memorable National Day celebration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bank of America : Sustainability at Bank of America ( SustainabilityatBankofAmerica2024Report ) </title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/bank-of-america-sustainability-at-bank-of-america-sustainabilityatbankofamerica2024report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/bank-of-america-sustainability-at-bank-of-america-sustainabilityatbankofamerica2024report/</guid>
      <description>The document discusses the company s commitment to achieving Net Zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2050 in its financing activities, operations, and supply chain. It sets interim 2030 Net Zero emissions targets, including financed emissions targets and sustainable finance commitments. These targets may evolve over time due to proposed legislative and regulatory changes in multiple jurisdictions, which could significantly impact future measurement, reporting, and the effectiveness of the company s sustainability efforts.  The company uses forward-looking statements, such as  anticipates,   targets,  and  expects,  to express its current expectations, plans, or forecasts. However, these statements are not guarantees of future results or performance and involve various risks, uncertainties, and assumptions that are difficult to predict and often beyond the company s control. Actual outcomes may differ materially from those expressed in these forward-looking statements due to factors like global socio-demographic and economic trends, energy prices, technological advances, climate-related conditions, legislative and regulatory changes, public policies, stakeholder engagement, data quality and availability, and the company s ability to implement sustainability initiatives.  The document also mentions that the content on referenced websites is not incorporated by reference into this document, and third-party website references and links do not imply an affiliation, sponsorship, or endorsement. The document was published on September 30, 2024, and contains Sustainability Information applicable to the company and its subsidiaries worldwide.  In summary, the company is committed to achieving Net Zero emissions by 2050, with interim targets set for 2030. However, the success of these efforts depends on various factors, including legislative changes, technological advancements, and the company s ability to implement sustainability initiatives. The company s forward-looking statements are subject to risks and uncertainties, and actual outcomes may differ from those expressed in these statements. The document also clarifies that the content on referenced websites is not incorporated by reference and that third-party website references and links do not imply an affiliation or endorsement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BARRON COVE to Premier at the Hamptons International Film</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/barron-cove-to-premier-at-the-hamptons-international-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/barron-cove-to-premier-at-the-hamptons-international-film/</guid>
      <description>American Picture House (APHP), an entertainment company specializing in financing and producing feature films and limited series, announced the premiere of the motion picture BARRON’S COVE at the Hamptons International Film Festival (HIFF) on October 6. The film, directed by Evan Ari Kelman, follows a grieving father, played by Garrett Hedlund, who kidnaps his son s Christian Convery, portrayed by Brittany Snow, in a desperate search for answers to his son s death. The story also involves the powerful politician father, Hamish Linklater, and a ruthless uncle, Stephen Lang, who uses his influence to control those around him.  Produced by APHP and several other production companies, BARRON’S COVE is a gripping thriller that explores the complexities of revenge and a flawed father s devotion to his son. The film showcases APHP s commitment to producing intelligent, thought-provoking content that aligns with ESG principles.  Bannor Michael MacGregor, CEO of APHP, expressed his pleasure in having BARRON’S COVE premier at HIFF, emphasizing the company s dedication to delivering high-quality films and shows with broad market appeal.  The press release also includes a disclaimer about forward-looking statements, highlighting the risks and uncertainties that could cause actual results to differ from those described in the statements. These risks include changes in technology and market requirements, delays in launching properties, difficulties in retaining key employees, and unforeseen difficulties that may develop with the process.  For more information about American Picture House and BARRON’S COVE, visit their website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.americanpicturehouse.com&#34;&gt;www.americanpicturehouse.com&lt;/a&gt; or contact Bannor Macgregor at 877-416-5558 or 917-699-8885.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big U . S . oil companies reveal massive payments to foreign governments</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/big-u-s-oil-companies-reveal-massive-payments-to-foreign-governments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/big-u-s-oil-companies-reveal-massive-payments-to-foreign-governments/</guid>
      <description>The three largest U.S. energy companies, Exxon Mobil Corp., Chevron Corp., and ConocoPhillips, disclosed payments to foreign governments totaling over US$42 billion in 2023, which is approximately eight times more than what they paid domestically. This disclosure, mandated by the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), was a result of a decade-long push by transparency advocates to shed light on the foreign financial transactions of Big Oil in its global pursuit for oil.  The United States has become the world s largest oil and gas producer, largely due to the Permian Basin in Texas and New Mexico. However, the disclosures reveal that about 90% of Exxon s global payments went to foreign governments, despite nearly a quarter of its global exploration and production earnings coming from the U.S. The company paid out US$22.5 billion in taxes, royalties, and other items overseas, with the United Arab Emirates, Indonesia, and Malaysia being the top recipients.  In contrast, Exxon made about US$2.3 billion in U.S.-based payments in 2023, including just US$1.2 billion to the U.S. Internal Revenue Service. Exxon s U.S.-based upstream earnings totaled US$4.2 billion, compared to US$17.1 billion in non-U.S. markets.  Chevron paid US$14.6 billion to foreign governments in 2023, with Australia alone receiving US$4 billion. The company paid just US$2 billion in the U.S. Chevron executives see the low or no royalty payments in the Permian Basin as a significant advantage, creating shareholder value.  ConocoPhillips disclosed that just US$1.3 billion of its total US$6.5 billion in global payments went to the U.S.  The disclosures were made possible by Section 1504 of the Dodd-Frank Act, which was adopted by the SEC in 2020 after a long battle involving a federal</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big US oil companies reveal massive payments to foreign governments</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/big-us-oil-companies-reveal-massive-payments-to-foreign-governments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/big-us-oil-companies-reveal-massive-payments-to-foreign-governments/</guid>
      <description>The three largest U.S. energy exploration companies, Exxon Mobil, Chevron Corp, and ConocoPhillips, paid over $42 billion to foreign governments in the previous year, which is roughly eight times more than their payments within the United States. This information was disclosed for the first time due to a new SEC requirement, which transparency advocates have been pushing for over a decade. The aim is to shed light on Big Oil s foreign financial transactions and assess whether U.S. taxpayers receive a fair share of the value from the U.S. s surge in oil and gas production.  In 2023, about 90% of Exxon s global payments, totaling nearly $25 billion, were made to foreign governments, despite nearly a quarter of its global exploration and production earnings coming from the U.S. The United Arab Emirates, Indonesia, and Malaysia were among the top recipients of Exxon s overseas payments. In contrast, Exxon made about $2.3 billion in U.S.-based payments, including $1.2 billion to the U.S. Internal Revenue Service.  Chevron paid $14.6 billion to foreign governments, with $4 billion going to Australia alone. The company made just $2 billion in the U.S. Chevron executives view the low overhead in the U.S. as a significant advantage, particularly in the Permian Basin, where about 75% of the land has low or no royalty payments.  ConocoPhillips paid $1.3 billion of its $6.5 billion total global payments to the U.S.  The disclosures were made possible by Section 1504 of the Dodd-Frank Act, which was adopted by the SEC in 2020 after a long battle involving a federal court vacating the SEC s first attempt and Congress blocking a second attempt. The rule aims to increase transparency and accountability between governments and the energy industry, in response to the growing ESG movement.  Overall, the disclosures reveal a significant disparity in the distribution of payments between the U</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celestica Recognized Among Lam Research 2024 Supplier Excellence Award Winners</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/celestica-recognized-among-lam-research-2024-supplier-excellence-award-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/celestica-recognized-among-lam-research-2024-supplier-excellence-award-winners/</guid>
      <description>Celestica Inc., a global leader in design, manufacturing, hardware platform, and supply chain solutions, has been recognized with a 2024 Supplier Excellence Award by Lam Research for its exceptional operational execution in its Johor, Malaysia facility. The award, presented during Lam s annual Supplier Day event, highlights Celestica s proactive and adaptable delivery, strategic inventory solutions, localized manufacturing, and outstanding customer support.  The award acknowledges Celestica s commitment to high standards in scalability, agility, quality, and environmentally sustainable and socially responsible business practices. It also emphasizes the importance of collaboration within the supply chain to drive progress towards a better world.  Kevin Walsh, Vice President of Capital Equipment at Celestica, expressed pride in the recognition and the dedication of the team. The company remains committed to continuous improvement and innovation, aiming to build on this success in the future.  Lam Research, a global provider of innovative wafer fabrication equipment and services to the semiconductor industry, collaborates with suppliers worldwide to source specialized materials and components. The 2024 Supplier Excellence Awards aim to celebrate excellence and underscore the collective responsibility of companies in the supply chain to act with purpose for a better world.  Celestica, with its customer-centric approach, partners with leading companies in various sectors to deliver solutions for their most complex challenges. The company s global expertise and insight are applied at every stage of product development, from concept to full-scale production and after-market services.  For more information on Celestica, visit &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.celestica.com&#34;&gt;www.celestica.com&lt;/a&gt;.  Source: Celestica International LP2024 GlobeNewswire, Inc., source Press Releases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certain BlackRock Closed - End Funds Announce Estimated Sources of Distributions</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/certain-blackrock-closed-end-funds-announce-estimated-sources-of-distributions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/certain-blackrock-closed-end-funds-announce-estimated-sources-of-distributions/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CleanTech Lithium PLC Announces Interim Results</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/cleantech-lithium-plc-announces-interim-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/cleantech-lithium-plc-announces-interim-results/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EiQ - World first end - to - end supply chain due diligence software</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/eiq-world-first-end-to-end-supply-chain-due-diligence-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/eiq-world-first-end-to-end-supply-chain-due-diligence-software/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EverDriven Welcomes Bridgette Brinkmann as Chief People Officer</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/everdriven-welcomes-bridgette-brinkmann-as-chief-people-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/everdriven-welcomes-bridgette-brinkmann-as-chief-people-officer/</guid>
      <description>EverDriven, a leader in Alternative Student Transportation, has announced the appointment of Bridgette Brinkmann as its new Chief People Officer. Brinkmann will be responsible for overseeing the company s human capital strategy, managing talent for a nationally distributed and expanding team, and spearheading initiatives related to culture, engagement, learning and development, ESG, and regulatory and compliance efforts.  Mitch Bowling, CEO of EverDriven, expressed his excitement in welcoming Brinkmann to the team, highlighting her impressive experience in leading teams for some of the world s largest companies and her ability to connect with people and drive intrinsic motivation. Brinkmann s extensive experience at purpose-driven companies such as Pfizer, Danone, Vail Resorts, and the hyper-growth startup Meati has equipped her with the skills to support EverDriven s growth while prioritizing its mission.  At Pfizer, Danone, and Vail Resorts, Brinkmann focused on leading change, building high-performing teams, and cultivating organizational culture. At Meati, she played a crucial role in expanding the startup s retail footprint to 7,000 stores, showcasing her ability to drive business growth while nurturing talent.  Brinkmann was drawn to EverDriven due to its potential to make a significant impact on people s lives. She is passionate about growing businesses and teams, but she finds it even more rewarding when they can positively impact the world. In her new role, Brinkmann will prioritize the evolution of EverDriven s culture to support expansion and growth, and she will focus on identifying and recruiting mission-driven talent who are eager to contribute to building an industry-leading organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flight Shame : Sweden Scraps Flight Tax Despite Emissions Rise</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/flight-shame-sweden-scraps-flight-tax-despite-emissions-rise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/flight-shame-sweden-scraps-flight-tax-despite-emissions-rise/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FPT Software Wins Job Creation Award at ESGBusiness Awards 2024</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/fpt-software-wins-job-creation-award-at-esgbusiness-awards-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/fpt-software-wins-job-creation-award-at-esgbusiness-awards-2024/</guid>
      <description>FPT Software, a subsidiary of FPT Corporation, has been recognized with the Job Creation Award—Vietnam at the ESGBusiness Awards 2024, marking its first win in this category. The company, with a global workforce of over 30,000 employees across 30 countries, has demonstrated a strong commitment to nurturing top talent in the global IT industry and promoting diverse and inclusive workplaces.  FPT Software s steady employment growth supports its parent company s goal of employing one million IT professionals by 2035. The company has established pathways for Vietnamese employees to gain international experience, with over 3,000 individuals working in its overseas branches. Additionally, FPT Software has attracted more than 3,500 foreign staff from 75 nationalities.  The company s commitment to diversity and inclusion is evident in its workforce composition, with women making up 39.6% of its employees and 33% of managerial roles. FPT Software also invests in continuous learning and growth opportunities for its employees, with an average of 31.7 hours of professional training annually.  In a recent initiative, FPT Software announced a 125 billion VND investment to provide training and career development opportunities to over 3,000 Japanese-speaking ICT professionals. This initiative, launched in collaboration with 15 universities, underscores the company s dedication to workforce development and creating employment opportunities that align with the evolving IT landscape.  Nguyen Tuan Minh, Chief Human Resources Officer of FPT Software, emphasized the company s focus on investing in education, training, and fostering a dynamic workplace environment to build a future-ready IT talent pool.  FPT Software has received numerous accolades, including Great Place to Work® Certifications across Asia Pacific, Japan, the United States, Vietnam, Germany, and the Philippines. The company was also awarded the BRONZE STEVIE® for Employer of the Year at the 2024 Stevie® Awards for Great Employers.  FPT Software, with $1 billion in revenue (202</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global X Solar ETF ( NASDAQ : RAYS ) Short Interest Up 23 . 8 % in September</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/global-x-solar-etf-nasdaq-rays-short-interest-up-23-8-in-september/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/global-x-solar-etf-nasdaq-rays-short-interest-up-23-8-in-september/</guid>
      <description>Global X Solar ETF (NASDAQ:RAYS) experienced a significant increase in short interest during September, with a total of 2,600 shares as of September 15th, marking a 23.8% rise from August 31st s 2,100 shares. The short-interest ratio stands at 0.3 days based on an average daily volume of 8,100 shares.  The ETF opened at $10.98 on a Monday, with a 50-day simple moving average at $9.95 and a 200-day simple moving average at $10.67. The stock has a 12-month low of $9.27 and a 12-month high of $13.63. The company s market cap is $7.91 million, with a negative price-to-earnings ratio of -49.85 and a beta of 1.08.  Institutional investor Albion Financial Group UT recently acquired a new position in Global X Solar ETF, purchasing 4,143 shares valued at approximately $49,000. This purchase accounted for roughly 0.73% of the company s holdings at the end of the most recent quarter. Overall, 9.99% of the stock is owned by hedge funds and other institutional investors.  The Global X Solar ETF (RAYS) is an exchange-traded fund based on the Solactive Solar index, which includes global solar energy companies selected based on their revenue generated from solar-related business and ESG criteria. Launched on September 8, 2021, the ETF is managed by Global X.  To stay updated on Global X Solar ETF, consider subscribing to MarketBeat.com s FREE daily email newsletter, which provides concise summaries of the latest news and analysts  ratings for the ETF and related companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Reduce the Risk of AI and Enhance Its Societal Impact</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/how-to-reduce-the-risk-of-ai-and-enhance-its-societal-impact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/how-to-reduce-the-risk-of-ai-and-enhance-its-societal-impact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid , multicloud to continue as the norm : HCLTech report</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/hybrid-multicloud-to-continue-as-the-norm-hcltech-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/hybrid-multicloud-to-continue-as-the-norm-hcltech-report/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HYCU® Appoints Brian Babineau As First Chief Customer Officer</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/hycu-r-appoints-brian-babineau-as-first-chief-customer-officer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/hycu-r-appoints-brian-babineau-as-first-chief-customer-officer/</guid>
      <description>HYCU, Inc., a rapidly growing leader in SaaS and multi-cloud data protection, has appointed Brian Babineau as its Chief Customer Officer. Babineau brings over 20 years of experience in customer-focused services and support organizations, having previously held key positions at Barracuda and EMC. His appointment comes as HYCU seeks to enhance the customer journey and achieve its business objectives.  Babineau s role at HYCU will involve ensuring customers derive maximum value from their technology investments while exceeding success and support expectations. He will join a customer-centric leadership team that prioritizes protecting and securing critical enterprise data.  HYCU, founded in Boston, Massachusetts, is known for its industry-leading NPS score of 91 and has raised $140M in VC funding. The company s R-Cloud platform offers unrivaled data protection, migration, disaster recovery, and ransomware protection to thousands of companies worldwide.  For more information about HYCU s data protection solutions, visit their website, follow them on social media, or connect with them on LinkedIn, Facebook, Instagram, and YouTube.  About HYCU: HYCU is the fastest-growing leader in the multi-cloud and SaaS data protection as a service industry. By providing true SaaS-based data backup and recovery to on-premises, cloud-native, and SaaS IT environments, the company offers unrivaled data protection, migration, disaster recovery, and ransomware protection to thousands of companies worldwide. The company s award-winning R-Cloud platform eliminates complexity, risk, and the high cost of legacy-based solutions, making it the #1 SaaS Data Protection platform. With an industry-leading NPS score of 91, HYCU has raised $140M in VC funding to date.  Attachment: Brian Babineau Joins HYCU as First Chief Customer Officer  CONTACT: Don Jennings HYCU, Inc. 617-791-1710  MENAFN30</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IAMGOLD Submits Formal 60 Days Notice to Sumitomo for Repurchase of 9 . 7 % Cote Gold Mine Interest</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/iamgold-submits-formal-60-days-notice-to-sumitomo-for-repurchase-of-9-7-cote-gold-mine-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/iamgold-submits-formal-60-days-notice-to-sumitomo-for-repurchase-of-9-7-cote-gold-mine-interest/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>InLife bags awards for ESG , governance</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/inlife-bags-awards-for-esg-governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/inlife-bags-awards-for-esg-governance/</guid>
      <description>Insular Life (InLife), a Philippine-based insurance company, received back-to-back accolades for its exemplary corporate governance and employee wellness program. The company was honored with the Four Golden Arrow Award at the ACGS Golden Arrow Awards ceremony, marking the seventh consecutive year of recognition by the Institute of Corporate Directors. This award, the highest among Philippine insurance companies, was based on InLife s outstanding performance in all ACGS categories, including rights of members, equitable treatment, stakeholder role, disclosure, transparency, and board responsibilities.  InLife s vice chairman, Luis la Ò, expressed gratitude for the recognition and highlighted the company s commitment to transparency, accountability, and fairness. He emphasized that this commitment has strengthened InLife s reputation and relationships with shareholders since 2018.  In addition to the ACGS award, InLife also received two awards at the ESG Business Awards 2024 in Singapore. The company was recognized for its Good Governance Award - Philippines and Workplace Wellness Programme Award - Philippines. These awards acknowledged InLife s dedication to corporate governance and sustainable practices in its core operations. InLife s commitment to prioritizing the diverse needs of its employees through flexible work arrangements, wellness initiatives, and comprehensive health benefits was also commended.  Overall, InLife s consistent recognition for its corporate governance and employee wellness program demonstrates the company s commitment to transparency, accountability, and sustainable practices, solidifying its reputation as a trusted institution in the Philippines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miraclon joins Consortium for Waste Circularity</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/miraclon-joins-consortium-for-waste-circularity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/miraclon-joins-consortium-for-waste-circularity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley Investment Management Completes 1GT Climate Private Equity Fund , at $750</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/morgan-stanley-investment-management-completes-1gt-climate-private-equity-fund-at-750/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/morgan-stanley-investment-management-completes-1gt-climate-private-equity-fund-at-750/</guid>
      <description>Morgan Stanley Investment Management announced the final close of the 1GT climate private equity fund at $750 million. The fund, which targets growth-oriented investments in North America and Europe, aims to avoid or remove one gigaton of carbon dioxide-equivalent (CO2e) emissions from the atmosphere by 2050. The investor group consists of institutions from Europe, Japan, and North America.  The 1GT team will utilize Morgan Stanley s resources to collaborate with portfolio companies, focusing on earnings growth, multiple expansion, and enhanced exit potential. Additionally, the team aims to increase climate change mitigation and improve environmental, social, and governance (ESG) monitoring and reporting.  Some of the fund s investments include Instagrid, a high-performance portable battery provider; Huel, a sustainable nutrition brand; and Everstream Analytics, a company specializing in sustainable supply chain services.  The 1GT fund is an Article 9 fund under the Sustainable Finance Disclosure Regulation, which mandates the integration of environmental or social characteristics into the investment process. Furthermore, half of the 1GT team s financial incentives are tied to achieving the target of avoiding or removing one gigaton of CO2e emissions by 2050.  This announcement was made on September 30, 2024, and is part of the broader FinSMEs initiative, which focuses on supporting small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) in the financial sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Namibia : Harnessing Hope - How Namibia Can Avoid the Traps of Oil Dependency</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/namibia-harnessing-hope-how-namibia-can-avoid-the-traps-of-oil-dependency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/namibia-harnessing-hope-how-namibia-can-avoid-the-traps-of-oil-dependency/</guid>
      <description>Namibia s burgeoning oil and gas sector, with significant foreign investments from companies like Total Energies, Shell, and Galp, has sparked optimism for economic growth. However, this development raises concerns about the  Dutch disease,  where a booming natural resource sector overshadows other vital industries such as agriculture and tourism. Between 2021 and 2023, Namibia attracted N$73 billion in foreign direct investment, with 45% concentrated in oil and gas. While this may boost the economy in the short term, it risks neglecting traditional sectors crucial for sustainable development.  Agriculture, supporting 70% of Namibia s population and contributing 5.1% to GDP, and tourism, employing over 100,000 individuals and contributing 3.5% to GDP in 2018, could suffer from this imbalance. The minister of agriculture, water, and land reform, Calle Schlettwein, warned against the overemphasis on oil and gas, noting that environmental concerns are often overlooked. He highlighted the industrial development of green hydrogen in one of Namibia s national parks, funded by the Environmental Investment Fund.  The  Africa Rising  narrative, exemplified by Mozambique s natural gas discoveries, has led to optimism about economic growth and development. However, Mozambique s experience shows that this optimism can be dashed by declining commodity prices and ongoing conflict. Zimbabwe s Marange diamond discovery also failed to deliver on its promises due to corruption.  To avoid similar pitfalls, Namibia must focus on investing in its traditional sectors, ensuring a balanced and sustainable approach to development. This will help build a resilient and inclusive economy, avoiding the risks associated with overreliance on a single sector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Challenges in Logistics Finance : Raco Investment Discusses Strategic Solutions for the Maritime Sector</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/navigating-challenges-in-logistics-finance-raco-investment-discusses-strategic-solutions-for-the-maritime-sector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/navigating-challenges-in-logistics-finance-raco-investment-discusses-strategic-solutions-for-the-maritime-sector/</guid>
      <description>Raco Investment, a leader in logistics and supply chain financing, offers strategic solutions to maritime businesses to navigate the complexities of logistics finance amidst a dynamic global trade environment. The firm addresses cash flow constraints through invoice financing, mitigates risks with structured trade finance, and leverages digital tools for real-time financial management.  Invoice financing is emphasized to bridge cash flow gaps, allowing companies to convert outstanding invoices into immediate cash, thus maintaining operational liquidity. Structured trade finance solutions, such as letters of credit and trade credit insurance, are advocated to manage risks like non-payment and currency fluctuations.  Digital tools are highlighted for their role in providing real-time insights into cash flow, expenses, and risk exposure, enabling data-driven decision-making. Freight financing is advised to manage volatile freight rates, ensuring predictable cash flow and financial stability.  Supply chain finance, including reverse factoring, is promoted to support suppliers with early payments, enhancing cash flow and supply chain efficiency. Green financing options are encouraged to align financial strategies with sustainability goals, attracting environmentally conscious investors and building sustainable supply chains.  Raco Investment also provides expert guidance on regulatory compliance, ensuring maritime businesses remain compliant and avoid potential pitfalls.  In summary, Raco Investment s strategic solutions empower maritime businesses to optimize financial management, reduce risks, and achieve sustainable growth in a competitive global market. The firm s expertise in invoice financing, structured trade finance, digital tools, freight financing, supply chain finance, and regulatory compliance helps maritime businesses thrive amidst the challenges of logistics finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Thin Film Solar Factory Turns Red State Green</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/new-thin-film-solar-factory-turns-red-state-green/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/new-thin-film-solar-factory-turns-red-state-green/</guid>
      <description>Alabama state officials and First Solar have inaugurated a new factory in Lawrence County, marking a significant step in the state s renewable energy journey. The $1.1 billion facility, expected to double the state s solar jobs, will produce 3.5 gigawatts of solar capacity annually, contributing to the US renewable energy profile. Despite Alabama s red state politics and low ranking in solar capacity, the factory s establishment is a testament to the state s commitment to clean energy.  First Solar, a global leader in thin film solar technology, has chosen Alabama for its newest factory, citing factors such as land cost, transportation access, and state incentives. The company s cadmium telluride (CdTe) technology offers advantages over conventional silicon solar panels, including lower costs, greater efficiencies, and a smaller environmental footprint.  The project has faced opposition from anti-ESG legislation, which seeks to protect the fossil energy industry from competition. However, First Solar s  Responsible Solar  approach aligns with ESG principles, emphasizing the company s commitment to the planet, communities, and customers.  Despite the state s low ranking in solar capacity and the passage of anti-ESG legislation, Alabama s new factory demonstrates the state s potential to contribute to the US s renewable energy goals. The facility will provide solar developers with a significant supply of solar panels, supporting the interstate market and promoting sustainable energy solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OSSIAM STOXX® EUROPE 600 ESG EQUAL WEIGHT NR UCITS ETF 1C ( EUR ): Net Asset Value ( s ) </title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/ossiam-stoxx-r-europe-600-esg-equal-weight-nr-ucits-etf-1c-eur-net-asset-value-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/ossiam-stoxx-r-europe-600-esg-equal-weight-nr-ucits-etf-1c-eur-net-asset-value-s/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Platinum | 3BL</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/platinum-3bl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/platinum-3bl/</guid>
      <description>Book a demo to explore the unique features of the 3BL platform, which stands out from other platforms previously encountered. This platform is specifically designed to cater to sustainability professionals and teams, offering a range of custom reports, insights, and editorial tools.  Key features include:  1. Quarterly executive business reviews: Provide valuable insights and analysis to help guide decision-making processes. 2. Editorial calendar planning: Assist in organizing and managing content creation and distribution. 3. Annual stakeholder perception survey: Gather feedback and measure the impact of sustainability initiatives on stakeholders. 4. Quarterly sustainability disclosure score: Track and report on sustainability performance to maintain transparency and accountability. 5. TriplePundit editorial blueprint: Offer a structured approach to creating compelling content for sustainability-focused publications. 6. Early access to research: Provide access to the latest studies and data to inform strategic decision-making.  The 3BL platform has proven to be a reliable partner in reaching key decision-makers and delivering content that engages and educates them on sustainability and ESG (Environmental, Social, and Governance) matters. The service provided has not only been exceptional but has also positively impacted Cummins  reputation as a company deeply concerned about sustainability.  By booking a demo, you can experience firsthand the unique capabilities of the 3BL platform and how it can help your organization enhance its sustainability efforts and engage with stakeholders effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pressmeddelande</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/pressmeddelande/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/pressmeddelande/</guid>
      <description>Wolters Kluwer, a prominent provider of professional information and software solutions, has achieved the highest ranking among AEX-listed large cap companies in The Netherlands in the 18th edition of the Dutch Female Board Index for 2024. The company, based in Alphen aan den Rijn, boasts a significant representation of women in its leadership, with 50% of the Executive Board, 50% of the Supervisory Board, and 40% of divisional chief executives being female.  The Dutch Female Board Index, compiled by Professor Mijntje Lückerath at the TIAS School for Business and Society, evaluates the presence of women in the Executive and Supervisory Boards of the 82 largest listed companies in the Netherlands. The 2024 results show an increase in the number of newly appointed female executives, rising to 32% from 13% a year earlier. The percentage of newly appointed female members at the Supervisory Board level remained stable at 53%.  Wolters Kluwer s commitment to gender diversity in its leadership positions is reflected in its impressive ranking in the Female Board Index. The company s dedication to promoting women in executive and supervisory roles contributes to a more inclusive and balanced corporate environment.  For more information on Wolters Kluwer and its achievements, visit the company s website at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.wolterskluwer.com&#34;&gt;www.wolterskluwer.com&lt;/a&gt;. The company can also be followed on social media platforms such as LinkedIn, Facebook, YouTube, and Instagram.  Wolters Kluwer, a global leader in information, software solutions, and services, serves professionals in various sectors, including healthcare, tax and accounting, financial and corporate compliance, legal and regulatory, and corporate performance and ESG. With annual revenues of €5.6 billion in 2023, the company operates in over 180 countries and employs approximately 21,400 people worldwide. The company s headquarters are located in Alphen aan den Rijn, the Netherlands.  Attachment:  &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tias.edu/nieuws-en-artikelen/item/recordaantal-ben&#34;&gt;https://www.tias.edu/nieuws-en-artikelen/item/recordaantal-ben&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmable Money - transforming financing for ESG and sustainability projects in the digital age</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/programmable-money-transforming-financing-for-esg-and-sustainability-projects-in-the-digital-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/programmable-money-transforming-financing-for-esg-and-sustainability-projects-in-the-digital-age/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qlik commits to UN Global Compact</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/qlik-commits-to-un-global-compact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/qlik-commits-to-un-global-compact/</guid>
      <description>Julie Kae, executive director of Qlik, emphasized the company s commitment to leveraging data and AI to support the UN s Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) and drive environmental, social, and governance (ESG) objectives. Qlik s partnership with the UN Global Compact reaffirms its dedication to providing organizations with the necessary tools to address complex global challenges, including climate action and human rights.  The UN Global Compact, a worldwide corporate sustainability initiative, has participants in 167 countries. Through this framework, Qlik aims to empower UN agencies and stakeholders to utilize data and AI for more transparent and effective decision-making. The collaboration with Qlik has strengthened the UN s ability to analyze and act on critical data, enhancing efficiency, transparency, and decision-making across various global initiatives.  Rumman Chowdhury, a founding member of Qlik s AI Council, highlighted the importance of expanding access to advanced data, analytics, and AI technologies to accelerate global development and address pressing challenges. Qlik s long-standing partnership with the UN Office for Information and Communications Technology (OICT) has helped overcome data silos and inconsistent governance, enabling the UN to make informed decisions across a range of initiatives.  Qlik s data integration platform plays a crucial role in driving progress on the 17 SDGs, empowering the UN to advance its global initiatives with greater efficiency and impact. The company s solutions support critical areas such as budget tracking, procurement, gender equality, peacekeeping troop deployments, capacity-development projects, and global crime statistics.  Recently, Qlik extended its support to the United Nations Framework Convention on Climate Change (UNFCCC), where its data and analytics solutions help accelerate the shift from climate mitigation to actionable, data-driven climate strategies. This partnership enables the UNFCCC to leverage AI to handle vast datasets from countries worldwide, ensuring quality and transparency in global climate reporting.  By joining the UN Global Compact, Qlik reinforces its role as a leader</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Realty Income Publishes Annual Sustainability Report</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/realty-income-publishes-annual-sustainability-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/realty-income-publishes-annual-sustainability-report/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Significant Metallurgical Advancement : Moving Toward a New Industry Standard for LiFePO4 Battery Feedstock</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/significant-metallurgical-advancement-moving-toward-a-new-industry-standard-for-lifepo4-battery-feedstock/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/significant-metallurgical-advancement-moving-toward-a-new-industry-standard-for-lifepo4-battery-feedstock/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sino - European Corporate ESG Best Practice Conference Recognizes China Taicang High - Tech Zone for Its Sino - German Collaboration , Driving ESG Development - Iberonews</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sino-european-corporate-esg-best-practice-conference-recognizes-china-taicang-high-tech-zone-for-its-sino-german-collaboration-driving-esg-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sino-european-corporate-esg-best-practice-conference-recognizes-china-taicang-high-tech-zone-for-its-sino-german-collaboration-driving-esg-development/</guid>
      <description>The Taicang High-Tech Industrial Development Zone (THIDZ) in Jiangsu Province, China, was recently honored as the  Best ESG Community in Sino-European Economic and Trade Cooperation  at the Sino-European Corporate ESG Best Practices Conference in Frankfurt, Germany. Since its establishment in 1993, THIDZ has fostered sustainable development, corporate social responsibility, and governance mechanisms, with a focus on key components for new energy vehicles, machine tools, and aerospace industries.  Over the years, more than 500 German companies have invested in the zone, contributing to an annual industrial output of over RMB 60 billion. The zone has also emphasized green technology and environmental protection, with projects like the Sino-German Energy Efficiency Network, which has achieved significant results in energy efficiency and carbon emission reduction.  In addition to industrial collaboration, THIDZ has made significant strides in vocational education, implementing Germany s dual vocational education system since 2001. This system has become a hallmark of the zone s industrial development and talent cultivation.  The zone has also improved its business environment, introducing policies to support enterprise development. The recognition at the conference highlights the success of THIDZ as a model community for Sino-German cooperation, showcasing achievements in industrial collaboration, talent development, cultural integration, and green growth.  For more information, please visit: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930313363/en/&#34;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930313363/en/&lt;/a&gt;  Contact: EncycloVision (Shenzhen) Brand Communication Co., Ltd. Eason Zhou Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:evisionsinfo@gmail.com&#34;&gt;evisionsinfo@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;  Images: - High-resolution: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930313363/en/&#34;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930313363/en/&lt;/a&gt; - Low-resolution: Not provided</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sino - European Corporate ESG Best Practice Conference Recognizes FAW HONGQI for Injecting Green Energy into Global Sustainable Development - Iberonews</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sino-european-corporate-esg-best-practice-conference-recognizes-faw-hongqi-for-injecting-green-energy-into-global-sustainable-development-iberonews/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sino-european-corporate-esg-best-practice-conference-recognizes-faw-hongqi-for-injecting-green-energy-into-global-sustainable-development-iberonews/</guid>
      <description>The Sino-European Corporate ESG Best Practice Conference recently recognized FAW HONGQI, a prominent Chinese automobile brand, for its significant contributions to global sustainable development through the integration of green energy. The company was awarded the  Best Case in International Environmental Protection Cooperation  for its efforts in promoting low-carbon and energy-saving products, transitioning its entire process towards green and low-carbon operations, and actively engaging in responsible international sales and operations in European markets.  FAW HONGQI announced its global strategy for new energy vehicles in January 2023, outlining its strategic vision, goals, and action plans. The company has focused on key technical directions and core technologies, while also establishing comprehensive life-cycle management mechanisms to enhance supplier management.  The company has successfully entered markets such as Norway, the Netherlands, Sweden, and Denmark, exporting high-end intelligent green new energy vehicles and jointly developing new energy channel networks with partners. FAW HONGQI has also been actively involved in environmental advocacy activities, promoting a green and low-carbon social atmosphere.  In its ESG case, FAW HONGQI emphasized the importance of low-carbon production and living in protecting the Earth, and committed to nurturing new productivity, perfecting the green manufacturing system, producing green products, and promoting green and low-carbon lifestyles. The company aims to contribute to the achievement of the United Nations  Sustainable Development Goals for 2030.  The recognition of FAW HONGQI at the Sino-European Corporate ESG Best Practice Conference highlights the company s dedication to sustainable development and its role in fostering a green and low-carbon future.  For more information, please visit: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930722214/en/Sino-European&#34;&gt;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20240930722214/en/Sino-European&lt;/a&gt; Corporate ESG Best Practice Conference  Contact: EncycloVision (Shenzhen) Brand Communication Co., Ltd. Eason Zhou Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:evisionsinfo@gmail.com&#34;&gt;evisionsinfo@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;  Images:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sovereign wealth funds inject $30 bln into mining over two years : FT Mining Summit</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sovereign-wealth-funds-inject-30-bln-into-mining-over-two-years-ft-mining-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/sovereign-wealth-funds-inject-30-bln-into-mining-over-two-years-ft-mining-summit/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terex Corporation Announces Pricing of Private Offering of $750 Million of 6 . 250 % Senior Notes Due 2032</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/terex-corporation-announces-pricing-of-private-offering-of-750-million-of-6-250-senior-notes-due-2032/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/terex-corporation-announces-pricing-of-private-offering-of-750-million-of-6-250-senior-notes-due-2032/</guid>
      <description>Terex Corporation, a global manufacturer of materials processing machinery and aerial work platforms, has priced its private offering of $750 million in 6.250% senior notes due 2032 at par. The proceeds from this offering, along with new term loan borrowings and cash on hand, will be used to complete the acquisition of Dover Corporation s Environmental Solutions Group (ESG) subsidiaries and assets. The Notes and related guarantees will be offered to qualified institutional buyers and certain non-U.S. persons in transactions outside the U.S. under Rule 144A and Regulation S. The expected closing date for the Private Offering is October 8, 2024.  Concurrently, Terex plans to amend its existing credit agreement to increase its revolving credit facilities to $800 million and extend the maturity to the fifth anniversary of the Acquisition. A new term loan facility will also be established, maturing on the seventh anniversary of the Acquisition, with an anticipated total borrowing amount of up to $1,250 million.  This press release contains forward-looking statements about future events and financial performance, subject to risks and uncertainties. Terex s actual results may differ materially from these statements due to various factors, including the consummation of the Private Offering, Acquisition, and Amendment.  About Terex: Terex is a global manufacturer of materials processing machinery and aerial work platforms, serving industries such as maintenance, manufacturing, energy, recycling, minerals, and construction. The company offers products and solutions that help customers reduce their environmental impact, including electric and hybrid offerings, products supporting renewable energy, and products aiding in waste material recovery. Terex products are manufactured in North America, Europe, Australia, and Asia and sold worldwide.  Contact Information: Derek Everitt VP Investor Relations Email: [email protected]  Source: Terex Corporation News published on September 30, 2024.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tesco and Sainsbury  misleading shopper over recycling schemes</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/tesco-and-sainsbury-misleading-shopper-over-recycling-schemes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/tesco-and-sainsbury-misleading-shopper-over-recycling-schemes/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas Stock Exchange Names Nasdaq , NYSE Veterans to Top Jobs</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/texas-stock-exchange-names-nasdaq-nyse-veterans-to-top-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/texas-stock-exchange-names-nasdaq-nyse-veterans-to-top-jobs/</guid>
      <description>The Texas Stock Exchange (TXSE) has announced the hiring of executives from Charles Schwab Corp., Nasdaq Inc., and the New York Stock Exchange (NYSE) to build a leadership team ahead of its planned operations in the upcoming year. Cam Smith, a former SEC employee, will become the global head of trading, while Jeffrey Brown joins as general counsel and chief regulatory officer. Nicole Chambers from Nasdaq will serve a similar role for TXSE Group Inc.  The TXSE has raised $135 million and plans to file registration documents with the SEC soon. The exchange has the support of major investors like BlackRock Inc. and Citadel Securities. It aims to challenge the NYSE and Nasdaq in Texas  bid to attract more financial services industry jobs.  TXSE will be headquartered in Dallas, which has been gaining financial jobs from companies like Goldman Sachs Group Inc. and Charles Schwab. The exchange will not require companies to meet any environmental, social, and governance (ESG) thresholds, aligning with the state s efforts to reduce burdensome regulations for businesses.  Marc Cunningham, former regional head of capital markets for the NYSE in Houston, will be the global managing director. Richard Fisher, former Federal Reserve Bank of Dallas president, will serve as a strategic adviser. Brett Redfearn, former SEC director, will also be a strategic adviser.  TXSE s board includes Tom Long, co-CEO of Energy Transfer LP, Paul Foster, founder of Western Refining Inc., Alex Bussandri, global head of strategy at Citadel Securities, Tyson Tuttle, former CEO of Silicon Labs, and former Texas Governor Rick Perry.  The TXSE s establishment is seen as apolitical, with the aim of providing a competitive alternative to the NYSE and Nasdaq. The exchange s all-electronic trading operations are set to begin next year, bolstering Dallas  growing financial industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chronicle - Breaking news</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/the-chronicle-breaking-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/the-chronicle-breaking-news/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The power to make a difference - BusinessWorld Online</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/the-power-to-make-a-difference-businessworld-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/the-power-to-make-a-difference-businessworld-online/</guid>
      <description>Ruth Yu-Owen, President and CEO of Upgrade Energy Philippines (UGEP), exemplifies resilience and visionary leadership in the renewable energy sector. Her journey began in Zamboanga City, where she sold candies as a young entrepreneur. Despite failing the Certified Public Accountant Licensure Exam, she pursued a career in sales, leading to senior positions in an international freight forwarding company. The loss of her job at its peak propelled her into the renewable energy industry, where she founded PhilCarbon in 2006.  In 2016, Ruth partnered with Belgian company Upgrade Energy to establish UGEP, focusing on rooftop solar projects for the commercial and industrial segment. The company offers comprehensive services, including engineering, procurement, construction, operations, maintenance, and project financing for renewable energy projects. Under Ruth s leadership, UGEP completed the Philippines  largest solar rooftop project for a major conglomerate in Batangas, with a capacity of 13,800 kilowatt-peak.  Despite facing challenges, such as opposition to a wind farm project in Sagada and missed opportunities for government incentives, Ruth invested her personal savings to keep her business afloat and prioritized her team s welfare. Her commitment to integrity, continuous learning, and ethical standards is evident in her active participation in governance programs and various committees and boards.  Ruth s influence extends to championing environmental, social, and governance (ESG) principles, establishing new benchmarks for sustainability in the energy sector. UGEP s employment practices reflect a 50-50 gender balance and a commitment to employee well-being, mirroring Ruth s belief in diversity, inclusiveness, and social responsibility.  Looking ahead, UGEP aims to achieve a growth target of 500 megawatts (MW) of renewable energy utility scale and 200-MW of rooftop solar by 2028 under Ruth s leadership. She has earned recognition as one of the  Most Influential Filipino Women on LinkedIn  and continues to serve as</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webinar – AI - driven geothermal emissions transparency &amp; compliance , 4 October 2024</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/webinar-ai-driven-geothermal-emissions-transparency-compliance-4-october-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/webinar-ai-driven-geothermal-emissions-transparency-compliance-4-october-2024/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is the future of African oil and gas funding and exploration ? </title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/what-is-the-future-of-african-oil-and-gas-funding-and-exploration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/what-is-the-future-of-african-oil-and-gas-funding-and-exploration/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WNS ( Holdings ) Limited : WNS and Uniqus Join Forces to Offer Sustainability and Technical Accounting &amp; Reporting Consulting Services</title>
      <link>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/wns-holdings-limited-wns-and-uniqus-join-forces-to-offer-sustainability-and-technical-accounting-reporting-consulting-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://green-washer.com/en/greenwashing/2024-09-30/wns-holdings-limited-wns-and-uniqus-join-forces-to-offer-sustainability-and-technical-accounting-reporting-consulting-services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
